Connor Robinson Studying BA(Hons) Digital Media and Communications

West Yorkshire – Full Driver's Licence Email: ConnorARO@protonmail.com https://connorar.com/

Personal Summary:

A confident Digital Media undergraduate with a strong work ethic and an aspiration to work in webdevelopment; with 4 years of digital media experience ranging from freelance content creation to web design. A strong researcher with great intuition and an ability to quickly adapt to any given situation. Thrives on challenge. Enjoys finding solutions, being pushed to the limits, and learning new skills, whether that be a new coding language, figuring out video editing software or photography. Organises, plans, prioritises effectively, and meets deadlines.

Technical Skills:

SEO, YouTube Algorithm, Sony Vegas, Adobe Suite (Photoshop, Lightroom and Premiere), Office software, WordPress, HTML & CSS, Photography & Videography (DSLR, Mobile and Mirrorless Systems), Avid, iNews, XLR Microphones, Audio Interfaces / Audio Mixers, audacity, OBS, Social Media sites (YouTube, Twitch, Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, and Snapchat), Windows, Mac, and Linux Systems

Education:

University of Huddersfield
September 2021 - Present
Digital Media and Communications BA(Hons) With Sandwich year
Huddersfield New College
September 2019 - July 2021
Creative Media BTEC 3 A-Level Equivalent (Distinction* Distinction* Distinction)

Work Experience:

Videographer at Reliance Precision (Internship) July 2023 – Present

- Working in the design and communications department managing the videography side of the business.
- Writing up scripts and storyboards for videos.
- Doing photography as well to aid the team.
- Using all areas of the adobe suite to work effectively with my team.

Crew Member at McDonalds (Part-time) June 2021 – June 2023

- Working in a team, to ensure that quality and speed is maintained throughout orders.
- Handling customer requests and communicating requests to kitchen staff to ensure that the customer gets what they want.
- Problem solving such as helping customers with POS system and the McDonalds app.
- Participating in various online training courses such as advanced food hygiene and preparation, advanced customer service training and cleanliness courses.

Digital Media Experience:

Web-design for Cool Cat Gang June 2023 – June 2023

- Designed the main foundations of the website using WordPress.
- Worked collaboratively with a team who would provide other assets for the site.
- Used data scraping to gather pictures of each team member.
- Added custom HTML and CSS to the site so that the design was smoother across mobile platforms.

Web-design for Robinson Fencing October 2022 – December 2022

- Front-end and Back-end web development using WordPress.
- Managing content that is used e.g., pictures and product descriptions ensuring that product descriptions are appropriate for SEO.
- Programming elements for the website using HTML and CSS.
- Check and fix for bugs, ensure links work, user interfaces and accessibility for all pages.

Digital Media and Communications at Huddersfield University September 2021 – Current

- Designed and maintained a professional website based on my interests (Cars) using WordPress, CSS, and HTML. Sourced, edited images. Wrote articles embedded video.
- Made a podcast and a YouTube video based on the local area using software such as Vegas, Adobe Audition, Adobe Premiere and Audacity. Created scripts, edited.
- Managed a blog based on Media products; wrote 400-word articles on growth of various social networking platforms using Wix as a base to host the blog.

Freelance Content Creator (2,000 Followers 130 monthly subs) January 2018 – July 2021

- Collaborated with other creators within the field of gaming content creation.
- Produced 2 videos a week, 5 live streams a week providing followers a full week of varied content. Vlogs. Gaming Tutorials. Discussions on recent news and themes.
- All videos, graphics, scripts, and edits undertaken using Sony Vegas, Adobe Premiere, Photoshop, OBS, and Audacity software. 10 15-minute videos on varied themes.
- Sold merch to my audience to increase income and raised money to various charities.

Interests:

The majority of my interests lie within tech and social media; I am heavily interested in the algorithms and the secrets behind them. A lot of my free time is spent in Sublime an IDE that I use for coding websites in HTML and CSS; if I am not spending time coding I am using Sony Vegas to edit videos either for university or for small passion projects. I am also a strong believer in looking after myself, so I attend 3 Muay Thai classes a week to keep healthy both physically and mentally.

D	_af	or	ra	n	ce	•	
К	еı	e	ıe	n	СE	5	ī

Available upon request.